STEPHEN SCHOOLEY

FULL STACK
WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

226-341-8098
SCHOOLEY.SA@GMAIL.COM
WWW.STEPHENSCHOOLEY.CA
WWW.GITHUB.COM/SCHOOLEYSA

PROFILE

Utilizing a multitude of frameworks and languages, I create contemporary, responsive and accessible web design. I have abundant experience executing provided designs with clean, modular and reusable code, as well as using my practiced eye for perfection, to deliver an exemplary user experience.

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS/SCSS
- Responsive and Accessible Design
- JavaScript
- RESTful APIs
- Typescript
- React and other JS frameworks
- Node.JS
- Version control & collaboration using Git/GitHub
- Shopify and WordPress (Liquid/PHP)

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATE

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY | 2021

BACHELOR OF MUSIC

WILFRED LAURIER UNIVERSITY | 2012 - 2016

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Q4 INC. | NOV 2021 - JAN 2023 (CONTRACT)

- Created uniquely branded Investor Relations websites for major companies using HTML, CSS (SASS) and JavaScript with a variety of libraries and REST API integrations
- Accurately produce fully accessible and responsive site from provided Figma designs
- Enhanced functionality of templates used company wide through work on the Optimizations Team
- Manage projects in a Scrum framework from kickoff through design, development, QA and deployment using Asana, JIRA and GitHub

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

Q4 INC. | NOV 2021 - JAN 2023 (CONTRACT)

- Created uniquely branded Investor Relations websites for major companies using HTML, CSS (SASS) and JavaScript with a variety of libraries and REST API integrations
- Accurately produce fully accessible and responsive site from provided Figma designs
- Enhanced functionality of templates used company wide through work on the Optimizations Team
- Manage projects in a Scrum framework from kickoff through design, development, QA and deployment using Asana, JIRA and GitHub